=My Fairy Doctor= =Episode 29=
= My Fairy Doctor = = الحلقة 29 =
She was born
ولدت
with Qi Deficiency.
مع نقص Qi.
She suffers fatigue
إنها تعاني من التعب
and is lack of energy.
ونقص الطاقة.
Can it be cured?
هل يمكن علاجه؟
There is no cure
لا يوجد علاج
for this disease.
لهذا المرض.
It can only be treated slowly.
لا يمكن علاجها إلا ببطء.
Again?
ثانية؟
I'm so tired
أنا متعب جدا
of hearing these words.
لسماع هذه الكلمات.
You claim to have a hundred years of history
أنت تدعي أن لديك مائة عام من التاريخ
and that's all you can do?
وهذا كل ما يمكنك فعله؟
Father.
أب.
I feel congested in my chest.
أشعر باحتقان في صدري.
Lili.
ليلى.
I'm out of breath.
لا أستطيع التنفس.
What’s wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Dr. Wen.
دكتور ون.
I'll get the medicine.
سأحضر الدواء.
Quick.
سريع.
This sachet
هذا الكيس
is called "The Healer".
يسمى "المعالج".
It provides relief for
يوفر الإغاثة ل
hundreds of minor illnesses.
مئات من الأمراض البسيطة.
Lili, smell this.
ليلى ، شم هذا.
Lili.
ليلى.
How do you feel?
ما هو شعورك؟
I feel much better.
أشعر أفضل بكثير.
What kind of medicine is this?
أي نوع من الأدوية هذا؟
Mr. Liu.
السيد.  ليو.
We have another doctor.
لدينا طبيب آخر.
He developed this.
طور هذا.
Maybe
يمكن
he can treat her.
يمكنه علاجها.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
I've given you a chance.
لقد منحتك فرصة.
I hate quacks like you the most.
أكره الدجالين مثلك أكثر.
Leave now.
ارحل الآن.
Do you mean Dr. Tang Qinjian?
هل تقصد الدكتور تانغ كينجيان؟
Yes.
نعم.
Father.
أب.
I want to give it a try.
اريد اعطائها محاولة.
One last chance.
فرصة اخيرة.
You go and get Dr. Tang.
اذهب واحضر الدكتور تانغ.
If he can't cure my daughter's disease,
إذا لم يستطع علاج مرض ابنتي ،
I will immediately
سأفعل على الفور
demolish your clinic
هدم عيادتك
and your whole family
وعائلتك بأكملها
must leave right away.
يجب أن تغادر على الفور.
Okay.
تمام.
That's a deal.
هذا اتفاق.
Ancestor.
سلف.
It's all my fault
هذا كله خطأي
for what happened to the clinic.
لما حدث للعيادة.
Please help us.
ساعدنا من فضلك.
I will come every day and honour you.
سآتي كل يوم وأكرمك.
Qizi.
بنت.
What exactly happened that day?
ماذا حدث بالضبط في ذلك اليوم؟
Why don't you re-enact the scene?
لماذا لا تعيد تمثيل المشهد؟
I don't think that's necessary.
لا أعتقد أن هذا ضروري.
It's embarrassing.
إنه محرج.
Give it a try.
جربها.
It won't kill you.
لن يقتلك.
He's right, Qi.
إنه على حق يا تشي.
This is our last resort.
هذا هو الملاذ الأخير لنا.
All right.
حسنا.
I'll try.
سأحاول.
Ancestors.
أسلاف.
You were all professional
كنتم كلكم محترفون
and respectable,
ومحترمة ،
but why did you bring up such a narrow-minded man like my father?
لكن لماذا رتبت برجل ضيق الأفق مثل والدي؟
That doesn't work.
هذا لا يعمل.
Is it not this?
أليس هذا؟
So please
إذن من فضلك
come out and talk to him.
تعال وتحدث معه.
Qi.
تشى.
Are you cursing your father to die early?
هل تشتم والدك حتى يموت مبكرا؟
It was out of anger.
كان من الغضب.
Fine.
بخير.
I won't argue with you on this.
لن أجادل معك في هذا.
Think again.
فكر مرة اخرى.
What happened that night?
ماذا حدث في تلك الليلة؟
I think
أظن
there was thunder
كان هناك رعد
and it was raining heavily.
وكانت السماء تمطر بغزارة.
I have an idea.
لدي فكرة.
♪Light up all the stars♪
♪ تضيء كل النجوم
♪Wish for staying with you forever♪
♪ أتمنى البقاء معك إلى الأبد
♪You're like the thriving Tang dynasty♪
♪ أنت مثل سلالة تانغ المزدهرة ♪
♪No matter if we're fated or not♪
♪ لا يهم إذا كنا قدّرنا أم لا
♪We still love each other♪
♪ ما زلنا نحب بعضنا البعض